# **MUHAMMAD FAIQ MUBAROK**

South Purwokerto, Banyumas

**%** +62 821 1774 8606

■ faigmubarok@gmail.com

Six semester Information Systems student at Telkom University Purwokerto, specializing in full-stack web development with MERN Stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js). Experienced in building responsive interfaces and scalable backends, and committed to continuously improving the quality of work through the latest technology and best practices. My focus is on creating applications that are functional, provide an optimal user experience, and are completed on time.

# **Project Experience**

## PATANI - Fullstack Developer

September - December 2024

Platform connecting investors and farmers to fund agricultural, fisheries and livestock projects.

- Building UI with React.js and styling using Tailwind CSS for responsive design.
- Managed application routing with React Router DOM and connected APIs using Axios.
- Manage application state using React State Management to maintain data consistency.
- Designed backend with Django and developed REST API using Django Rest Framework (DRF).
- Implemented JWT for secure user authentication.
- Using SQLite3 for managing application data in the database.

#### U Kost - Frontend Developer & System Analyst

January - June 2024

A boarding house search platform that makes it easy for renters and property owners to connect and find a place to live.

- Analyze and design application systems to ensure functional and non-functional requirements are met, and processes are efficient and easy to use.
- Assist in designing flowcharts and use cases to map application workflows, ensuring the system runs according to business needs.
- Building the U Kost application UI using HTML, Tailwind CSS, and JavaScript DOM to create a responsive and interactive user interface.

# Organization & Committee

Dies Natalis Sistem Informasi 7

September - December 2023

Person In Charge

Information Systems Student Association

August 2023 - December 2024

Human Resource Development

Intern Information Systems Student Association

October 2022 - January 2023

Social Development

### **Education**

Halofina (Studi Independent)

Web Developer Financial Platform

Codepolitan (IT Bootcamp)

Fullstack Developer

Telkom University Purwokerto

Bachelor of Information Systems | GPA 3.90

MA Husnul Khotimah

Natural Sciences (IPA)

September - December 2024

July - November 2024

...,

September 2022 - Now

July 2019 - May 2022

## **Additional Information**

#### **Technical Skills**

- Tailwind CSS (Intermediate)
- Javascript (Intermediate)
- React JS (Intermediate)
- Node JS (Beginner)
- Express JS (Beginner)
- Python (Beginner)

- MySQL (Beginner)
- MongoDB (Beginner)
- Git (Intermediate)
- Github (Intermediate)

#### Non Technical Skills

- Communication
- Leadership
- Creativity
- Team Collaboration
- Problem Solver
- Analytical Thinking

#### **Portfolio**

https://faiqmubarok.vercel.app/